today I want to break down the process
for you of making an irresistible offer
for your coaching or online course
business if you've been trying to sell
your products online having new
resistable offer is the number one thing
that dictates if you can actually make
the kind of money that you want to make
most people get this wrong and it has
nothing to do with what you actually do
or the framework in this training I'm
going to be breaking down the process
for you of how to create the best
irresistible offer that gets the most
sales how we've been able to make over $
hundred million in sales in our own
irresistible offers and how you can
translate this whether you're just
making your first 5,000 10,000 $225,000
in your own business and how this is
going to actually catapult you into
success if you've been struggling to get
results for those of you I have not met
yet my name is Jeremiah Kowski and I've
been in the online coaching course and
mentorship space for the last 21 years
when I got started we were doing DVD and
CD products and that's how I got my
start was actually helping people put
those together since then I've learned
everything there is about Marketing
sales and have scaled multiple coaching
businesses to over $20 million per year
and I walk people through the process of
getting massive results in their
businesses from beginner to the results
that they could have only ever imagined
and having an irresistible offer is
really what breaks down what it takes to
succeed in your own online business and
so that's what we're going to be
breaking down here today is just not
just about pricing not just how you
present it not just how you put it
together but the whole Gambit of the
thing and we wouldn't be doing you a
good service if I didn't break it down
from the beginning steps of knowing who
do you help who is the person that
you're helping who is the person that
you're getting a result from I have a
process that I teach my clients we've
broken it down over the years to a
couple of different versions we either
have our s six steps to six and seven
figures or we have our three uh phases
of the business what I like is the three
phases and what this breaks down to is
number one you want to find
who the people are so if you have a
coaching business or a course business
finding who you can work with is the
most important thing number two you want
to
promote your offer to them and this is
what I work with my clients in my Elite
client growth accelerator program with
is how to once they know how to find
their clients how to actually promote it
get people on their email list and close
more sales and that's step number three
is closing sales and we really focus on
this
and this in my client growth accelerator
program this you can follow all my
YouTube videos and figure out this part
of it it's it's pretty simple I give
away most of this information for free
uh to people this I also do give away in
some of my trainings but this is what we
really spend a lot of the time when
people make an investment to work with
me they're going through okay how do I
actually get my stuff out there how do I
actually start promoting it how to
actually start to find those people and
so if you want to work with me on how to
craft your Niche your messaging your
sales offer how to become better at
sales how to have consistent sales how
to have the right messaging that has
massive impact so that you can have that
financial and time Freedom that you want
that's what my client growth exelator
provides for people and if you want to
jump into that you can find a link below
to either get on the waiting list or to
join us in there in our program so what
you have to do is you have to know where
those people
exist I'm assuming that you are you have
some kind of an idea of what you want to
do what you want to coach people on
right okay so you want to take that and
reverse engineer it into who that person
is that's going to most likely benefit
from that in your coaching or course
business the only reason that bu why
anybody's going to buy from you is
because there's a transformation from
where they are to where they want to be
people come and work with me because
they're struggling to get clients and
they want to know how to make they can
make seven figures how they can make
their first $5,000 online and everywhere
in between that process and what are the
steps to actually take so they don't
have to take a lot of risk so they
actually can get results and that's one
of the most important things when it
comes to building your irresistible
offer is getting your clients results
there's enough coaches that are out
there that don't get people results so
that's one of the number one things when
it comes to just a matter of Integrity
is making sure that you're getting
people results when they come into your
ecosystem okay so you want to figure out
and here's the best way to do this if
you're trying to reach everybody you're
not going to reach anybody and this is a
rule when it comes to building your
online course or coaching business
because trying to reach
everybody you're going to fall flat
because you're going to be spinning your
wheels in in way too many different
directions instead of being honed in on
what we call the two foundations of a
successful
offer is it something that you can bring
massive transformation in their life
have massive impact for create a result
for them okay and this comes from your
experience this comes from what you know
how to deliver this comes from your
framework this comes from your Genius
that you bring to the table okay this is
where you have receipts you have the
track record to prove that you're able
to do this number two and this one bit
controversial but it's one of the most
important parts of this is can I make a
ton of money from this okay so what I do
is I actually merge those two together
like like they become a well a tightly
wrapped strand if you can think of like
two strands of rope they're tightly
wound together between massive results
and massive amount of income as the two
most important things of deciding who do
I want to work with for instance there's
a there's a whole group of people out
there that I they love my content they
watch what I produce but they never buy
anything from me they never purchase
from me now again I love them they're
great they're amazing you might be one
of those people but my message is not
geared towards that group of people I
pretty much
imagine they don't exist in my mind and
I only imagine that I'm speaking to
somebody who is ready to become a client
of mine I'm imagining my dream client
who is that person that I want to work
with who is that person that has the
coaching business or the online course
business who can create massive impact
but they're not really able to attract
the right people to them and then they
want to know how do I sell to people at
scale so I can have consistent recurring
revenue of six and seven figures in
their business and so everything I
create is only geared towards that
specific type of person so what you want
to do is this when you're creating your
ears a spill offers you want to think
about who is that specific type of
person that I want to reach they're an
individual that hones in that that that
is dialed into one very key
aspect of all the things that you can do
yes what you do can help a lot of people
what I do can help a lot of people my
coaching program literally changes
people's lives my YouTube channel
changes people's lives when they apply
what I teach in
it but the fact of the matter is is that
I'm in the business to have a profitable
business that makes a lot of money and
so I'm going to gear every piece of
messaging that I have towards the type
of person I'm going to design every
offer that I have towards the type of
person their thinking their motivation
their dreams their aspirations their
goals that's based around those two
things can I get them a big
result and can I make a ton of money by
communicating with that person and we
weave those two together into what
creates the perfect offer because what
we're doing is we're making it tailored
tuned it's customized it's personalized
for that one person and that's what
makes it
irresistible we all have different
preferences we all have different things
that we're into we all have different
stuff that we like when you can create
an irresistible offer it's about
creating it that is so dialed in and by
the way it's not very hard to do that
because it's actually a lot easier to do
this than it is to not do it and that's
the really cool part about it is a lot
of people think oh it's a lot of work to
figure that out no because literally
you're only focused in on one person one
type of person and this is what we call
the on to many model so in the one to
many model we're reaching one specific
type of person there's one very specific
person that I have in mind that I know
that I can deliver results to that I
know that I can transform their life
that I know is going to buy from
me and every time that I create a piece
of content every time that I make a a
lead magnet an offer
it's
directly
geared in every single way in every
detail towards what that person desires
and craves because craving is one of the
biggest Parts about it we all have
things that we crave that we long for
sometimes we're embarrassed to talk
about them you know I can think back to
when I was single and not married I
craved to be able be married and so
that's a very specific type of Jeremiah
that I was back then back in
2014 before I met my wife and so I think
about that when it comes to building my
irresistible offers in my business is
that there's a very specific type of
person they
crave connection they crave um
authenticity
honesty um not being sleazy or slimy
they
crave knowing that it's going to get
them a result they crave certainty they
desire to know that it's going to work
for them and I know that when somebody
comes into my ecosystem that it will
work for them that it's going to produce
that result if they apply it if they do
the work if they go through that process
and there's a lot of people out there
that sure maybe I could connect with but
they don't fall into that category
because not everybody who's out there is
my business going to get those results
for we focus specifically on coaches and
course
creators Consultants mentors people that
have a framework a system and
information to take people from point A
to point B and and resolve all of the
the nitty-gritty aspects along the way
and so what you want to do is you want
to be able to know who that person is
that you're going to be able to
communicate with then you have to create
communication mechanisms this is what we
call them these are these are ways that
you show and demonstrate the value to
the right person and there's a number of
different ways that we can do this in
our business if we pull this up
here on the internet on social media on
YouTube gives us a great opportunity to
connect with the right people
and so what we do is we look at okay
what are their deepest desires you might
say I don't know what the deepest
desires of my Prospect are so that's
where you go and you put on your
detective hat and you become a little
bit like Sherlock Holmes and you start
having some fun digging deep into what
that deep desire is and you can do this
actively by asking people questions by
creating ways of connecting and engaging
with people one of the ways that we do
this
is that we'll create pieces of content
and by sheer
osmosis we have embedded inside of it
ways of asking people questions about
like what are their biggest struggles
what are the biggest things that they're
wanting to learn or grow in in their
business you know for instance if you're
watching this right now I'd love to know
that in the comments below is it is it
leads is it advertising is it is it
sales what is it and then from there we
create all of our offers around that
specific area that somebody is dealing
with now in the beginning we may
struggle to know what this is and so
what's really fun is is that if you
don't have clients
already let me back up if you do have
clients already you're even more further
ahead because you can literally just
take what those clients desire and
translate that right into your offer to
be one to many to be a group coaching
offer or a course if you don't have
clients already we can use artificial
intelligence
to simulate the mindset and the thinking
of our Target client and the person that
we want to work with Okay so we want to
keep this in mind what do we do what is
our framework what what is our
methodology and we start to craft a
message and a storyline that connects
with the people that we can help the
most and so what we do is we create on a
website what we call
a
lead magnet okay so our lead
magnet allows us to get people onto our
email list by solving one specific
problem that they have to get a quick
win of some kind and it's important that
you have a lead magnet that gets people
quick wins
because people are not going to buy from
you in your business business simply
because you have an incredible program
this is not 2012 anymore this is not
anymore that was
over gosh 12 years ago that was
over 10 years ago 8 years ago and so if
we think about this is that we're in a
different world in 2024 than we were
back then people engage on the internet
differently Co massively threw
everything out of whack and shifted the
global landscape of online marketing and
so now what we have to do is we have to
be able to get people quick wins to be
able to build trust with them and then
by building that trust with them we can
then get them to become our clients
whenever I make a piece of
content I would be silly to think that
people would just want to become a
client simply because I'm yapping and
opening my mouth and talking about
something of value but over time the
more people connect with me the more
quick wins that I get them the more
information that I share the more value
that I bring to
people it builds
trust and then those people join my
email list we have free classes that we
put together you'll you can find in the
description of this video right now we
have a free class that we've actually
put together all about building growing
your online course or coaching business
and so with that what we're able to do
is then we're able
to
nurture and another word that I like to
think of is
cultivate a relationship and a
connection with those people and so it
becomes this long-term thing that it
doesn't take a lot of time to do but
it's it's how often and how much they
have made a connection with us that
helps them see and believe and trust
that you can deliver the results so
remember we talked about you merge the
two things together you Del you can
deliver a result to
somebody and you can make a ton of money
from it so we show them that we can
deliver the result because they have to
believe it first by nurturing and
cultivating that trust and then what we
are able to do is we are able to make
our irresistible offer which solves the
big problem for them and this is going
to be based on an outcome what is one
big tangible outcome that you can
deliver to people and what we like to do
is we like to break this
down into what we call four
pillars three Transformations and one
big
outcome Okay so so the four pillars look
like this number one in my business we
help people dial in their Niche number
two we help them
optimize their
messaging number three we help them
promote their business and then number
four and this is the most important we
help them sell baby sell to make a ton
of money in their bus business and what
this does is this helps take people from
inconsistent
income to
consistent cash flow
okay so this is one layer these are the
four pillars of what we we work with
people in my program to do and in your
own program when you're selling to
people when you're creating an
irresistible offer is you're going to be
showing people the four pillars that you
have of what you do
so it mind consistent cash flow go from
low impact
to
massive
impact and then from over here we help
people go from not knowing how to
communicate being confusing with their
messaging to having
laser
focused Clarity on what to do next and
what that creates for people is
financial and
time freedom in their life so they're
not having to work 100 hours a week so
they can work just even 5 to 10 hours a
week build a business with their family
and make six and seven figures doing so
in a course or coaching
business and
so this breaks down
emotionally what we help people do what
you want to do is you want to break down
emotionally and
demonstrate how you help people so that
it feels really good and then you can
break down what is actually delivered
and so one of the ways that we like to
create for our
offers is you know will
include uh some courses will include
live training modules will include a
community and support
and most
importantly we're going to give people a
path
to
success and we're going to show them
that by becoming a part of our program
they're not just getting information in
the form of a course you can get
information anywhere you can get
information through YouTube you can get
information through tons of resources
we're not just going to have some live
calls that they can be part of honestly
that that that can be exhausting of all
that is is live
calls we're also going to provide
support and community and be able to
actually bring them into something with
like-minded people that are
accomplishing the same thing and then we
create a proven Pathway to success for
them that is going to deliver that
result and so we're able to structure
that in a way that is very attractive
and very appealing to our Prospect and
so when we when we break it all down and
we go back to the beginning stages of
the
process is you can go and start by
finding somebody on social
media you can find somebody through
YouTube and these are are our most uh
favorite resources right here and the
goal is to get them onto your email
list and then once they're on your email
list you can
nurture that trust with them so we're
going to go through a process of
nurture okay somebody just being on your
email list is just the first stage of
this process I find people put way too
much effort into making the social media
and YouTube Perfect when really all
you're trying to do is you're just
trying to make a connection so somebody
can join your email list and then from
there the reason why you want them on
your email list is so that you can
nurture them so that you can continue
that connection with value that you're
delivering the value gets delivered once
they're on the email list often times I
see a lot of coaches and Mentor is
trying to deliver a ton of value up here
when really this is more like an
advertisement this is more like a an
appetizer to the value that gets
delivered down here okay and so like yes
you deliver value up here but that's
just scratching the surface as to what
people get when they actually come into
your ecosystem join your email list
consume consistent amounts of content
that you deliver and you create a
framework for yourself to be able to do
this sustainably so that it's not going
to burn you out it's not going to take
you a ton of hours to do this and that's
something that we Mentor people with in
our coaching program and once you
nurture those
[Applause]
people that nurture builds trust in you
your product your company and the
transformation that you offer the result
that you deliver it builds it up to what
we call a level 10
trust
okay and the level 10 trust
comes when people believe that you can
deliver on what you
say that your program is going to give
them the promised result people are are
way too Savvy these days and they are
tired of all the BS and they don't just
trust somebody who says I can produce a
result for you yeah you and what army
show me your receipts show me the proof
prove to me that you can do it and so
what you got to do is you have to prove
to them that you can deliver that result
by nurturing that trust with people if
we're focused way too much on all of the
social media content and our landing
pages and the technology pieces
literally it never allows us to get to
the point where we can build trust and
nurture that relationship with people
and that's why people are wondering why
am I not getting sales because you're
focused on the wrong things and that's
why in my client growth accelerator
program we move you past that part of it
so you can actually start to gain the
momentum that you're looking for to be
able to build that trust and to close
those sales with your prospects once you
have that trust at a level of 10 with
the right people and they're in
there you can sell
them on your program and you will make a
ton of money by doing so because what
this is is this they will start to see
that it's the answer to everything that
they've been looking for everything that
they've been hoping exists everything
that they've been wanting up to this
moment in time wishing that they could
have and accomplish and so when you
create the right framework to do this
and it doesn't take a lot of effort it's
not a ton of work to do so it's actually
about simple messaging with one offer
spoken to one specific type of person
where you show up consistently and
deliver results and people will buy into
it because they want that transformation
they want the thing that you are
offering and so people ask me all the
time well Jeremiah what do I price it at
I'm going to be honest with you pricing
is very irrelevant when you do this
process yes I know pricing is relevant
pricing decides the quality of client
that you get you don't want to be the
cheapest
option and that's one thing I'll
recommend don't charge any less than
$500 for your offer and for most of you
you shouldn't be charging less than
$2,000 for your
offer because that's you're undercutting
yourself and a lot of you should
actually be charging 10,000 and even
$20,000 for your offers now again we
have clients that sell across the board
with those different offer sizes you
know my client growth exer program at
the time of this recording it's it's
$200 a month we have a limited time
where actually offering a free trial to
actually try our program out that's an
irresistible offer right there I'm
giving people I'm taking the risk away
and I'm giving them an opportunity to
jump in try it out and become a client
of ours to see the difference that it
makes being inside of our ecosystem and
so when you do this and you can show
people the results that you deliver they
will want to work with you they will
want to stay connected with you and this
creates engagement that goes deeper and
deeper and deeper and what you want to
do is you don't just want want a onetime
sale you want a recurring sale you want
something that you're going to get paid
again and again and again not just once
not just twice but every single month
from your prospects and this is where we
turn it into a subscription based model
where you have a membership where people
can jump in they can join and they can
pay you every single month to become a
part of that and that's what we have
found is the most consistent the most
profitable and the best way to not have
feaster famine months but where you can
you can take 6 months or even a year off
if you need to and still make multiple
six figures I my wife and I we had our
son two almost two years ago we have
another baby on the way and I've been
taking a bit of a micro sabatical even
over the last year and a half we' scaled
our business to seven figures and I'm
like all right I've been coasting
through this and yet we've consistently
made multiple six and seven figures
throughout that process by doing this by
having recurring Revenue that's coming
coming in okay and so this is proven
this works this will work with you this
will work for you in your business and
so again if you want to dive deeper into
this process I'd love to work with you
inside my accelerator program I'd love
to I'd love to help you get those
results jump in and I'll see you in
there we'll talk soon have a good one